Well you are a story teller
You are a good story teller
Depending on the song
Umm, I kind of look at the songs
more like love letters
Love letters?
When did you write your first song?
Remember?
Yeah, I was probably
Uh, I started writing songs
Well, I thought they were songs anyway
Probably when I was about 15
When I was around 18
I met up with a guy called Jim Vallance
And he was able to structure,
help me structure ideas
And teach me about the structure of song writing.
And I think once I learnt that
Because there is no master class for how
to write music
You just have to,
it has got to be something you feel.
And so if the reprise feels good
you bring it back
And that's more like what you call a chorus
So it's just about how the structure
so the song feels good as it sort of rambles on
How did you get into music anyway?
I got into music very very young
Basically from hearing the music in my house.
My father loves music
and I used to belong to a thing called the
Columbia Record Club
You probably remember it
and it basically what you do is
is you buy a few records then
and then they just give you a few records.
Something like that.
So I was like if you gonna get a few records
Can I have one too?
you know,
And that's how I found out about a lot of groups.